Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU), Hudson Valley Area Joint Board; Records apap050
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Columbia County Joint Board, 1938-1957; 1.44 cubic ft.
  - Unions In Columbia County, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Warp-Knit Inc., Organizing File, 1953; 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1946-1968; Undated; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains the records of the Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Board. The Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Board was chartered in 1948 and merged with the Columbia County Joint Board to form the Hudson Valley Area Joint Board in 1957. This series contains meeting minutes, arbitration documents, bylaws, constitutions, and correspondence.
  - Charter, 1948; 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, 1946; 1948-1949; 1954; 1956; 1958 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Employee Benefits from Textile Workers Union of America, ca. 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Local 282, Brandley Dye Works Inc., Organizing Files, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Local 464, By-Laws, ca. 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Local 464, Capitol Piece Dye Works Inc., Arbitration, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Local 464, Garnerville Dye Works, Contracts, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Local 673, Dutchess and Lockwood, By-Laws, ca. 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Local 673, P.V.M Corporation, Contract, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Local 683, United Wire Goods, By-Laws, ca. 1951 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 683 United Wire Goods, Contracts, 1949-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Local 898, S. Stroock Co., Arbitration, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Local 898, S. Stroock Co., Inc., By-Laws, 1946; 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Local 898, S. Stroock Co., Inc., Contracts, 1951; 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Local 898, S. Stroock Co., Minutes, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Local 898, S. Stroock Co., Minutes of Pension Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 898, S. Stroock Co., Inc., Strike, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Local 982, Garnerville Holding Corp., Contracts, 1948; 1950-1952; 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Local 988, Tex-Ray Fabrics Inc., Arbitration, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Local 988, Tex-Ray Fabrics By-Laws, ca. 1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Local 988, Tex-Ray Fabrics Inc., Contracts, 1948-1949; 1951; 1953 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Local 1001, Steinfield Fabrics Co., By-Laws, ca. 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Local 1001, Steinfield Fabrics Co., Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Local 1001, Steinfield Fabrics Co., Contracts, 1948; 1951-1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Local 1001, Steinfield Newburgh, Minutes, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Local 1032, Printex Corporation of America, Arbitration, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Local 1032, Printex Corporation of America, By-Law, ca. 1950 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Local 1032, Printex Corporation of America, Contracts, 1950-1951; 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Local 1088, Hand Prints Inc., Arbitration, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Local 1088, Hand Prints Inc., Contract Negotiation, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Local 1088, Hand Prints Inc., Minutes, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Local 1121, Winston Prints Inc., Arbitration, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Local 1121, Winston Prints Inc., Contract, 1950-1951; 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Local 1121, Winston Prints Inc., Minutes, 1954; 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills Inc., Arbitration, 1950; 1952; 1954 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills Inc., Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills Contract, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Local 1122 Faith Mills Inc., Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills Inc., Grievance Meeting Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills Inc., Meeting Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Local 1122, Faith Mills Inc., Newspaper Clippings, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Local 1277, Insl-x, Contracts, 1952-1953; 1955 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Local 1318, Price Fire Waterproofing Co., By-Laws, ca. 1960 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Local 1318, Price Fire Waterproofing Co., Charter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Local 1318, Price Fire Waterproofing Co., Contracts, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Local 1338, Atlas Fibres Co., Inc., Contracts, 1953-1957 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Local 1420, By-Laws, ca. 1946 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Local Unknown, Storm King Prints Inc., Contracts, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Local Unknown, Contracts, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Lockwood Duchess Inc., Organizing File, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Mastic Tile Corp, Organizing File, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Mid-Hudson Valley Jt. Bd, Newspaper Clippings, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Mid-Hudson Valley Minutes and Meetings, 1950; 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Officers of Locals and the Joint Board, 1949-1953 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Board, Organizing Files, 1953; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Organizing Leaflets, 1949-1950; 1953-1956 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Pamphlets from the Textile Workers Union of America, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Mid-Hudson Valley Joint Board, Reports to International, 1949; 1953; 1955 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Star Expansion Industries Corp., Organizing File, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - TWUA Ritual, ca. 1953 (Box 1, Folder 56)